Hi everyone, so in this video, I just wanted to give one more update.
Like since this update dash profile is a put method, okay, it's update method.
That's why I've changed this route.post to put, okay.
So make sure to make this one change also and also you can go to like several of these
folders and somewhere I have done some mistake here, okay.
So like missing here, find by ID and update.
So this was some error that was causing some issues for me, okay.
So make sure to check all of these files and also in this, make sure to implement the
course policy as well.
Make sure you don't miss that otherwise when you will be uploading your photos or profile
pictures, you will be getting some kind of errors, okay.
And what else can I say you?
So these are the two things and second thing is that let's go to this frontend and this
authstore.js and this is the function for update profile, okay.
So last update task profile, make sure to implement the correct changes here, okay.
And if you go to testing these things, okay, let's go here, a face to bunch of issues here,
that's why I'm telling you.
So log in successfully profile, so as you can see you have uploaded this profile successfully
if you want to just change so you can do this image, yeah, okay.
So as you can see this is updating successfully, make sure to develop the changes of your
own or if some issues arises, please mark those issues and comment below this session,
okay.
[BLANK_AUDIO]